Excuse me, sir. Quick question for
you, man. Is this your Rolls Royce?
Yes, it is.
What do you do for a living?
Finance.
Sales. And I would tell you, if
anybody wanted to get rich, anyone, learn sales,
learn leadership, and this market will
reward you in ways you've never imagined.
I own a real estate brokerage.
What's the most amount of money that you
guys have sold in revenue in one year?
$1.4 billion.
Did you end up selling your company?
I took it public in
1993, and I retired in 1995.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
$200 million.
Okay. I'm going to make nine figures plus this year.
$20 million.
We were doing almost a
billion dollars a year in revenue.
You were doing almost a billion dollars?
Billion, yes.
What was the biggest thing that
took you to a billion-dollar company?
Very simple.
The city of Scottsdale is home to
over 13,000 millionaires and even five billionaires.
And in this video, we're going to be
going all over the entire city asking multi-millionaires
and even one of those billionaires how they
became wealthy and how you can start your path
to becoming financially free in 2023.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
$20 million.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yes.
Yeah?
Multiple times.
I've been rich and I've been
poor at least a couple of times.
I prefer rich, by the way.
It's a lot more fun.
But you hear the saying, the
rich get richer, the poor get poorer.
Somebody's stuck in that cycle of poverty.
What are some actual steps that
they can take to break that cycle?
You stay away from toxic people.
Think big, but you always got to be learning.
Otherwise, you can be on a treadmill doing
the same thing for the next 20 years.
I love it.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
Finance.
And how long have you been in the business for?
25 years.
So did you become a business owner?
Yes.
I've never liked working for somebody.
And what's the most common mistake that
you see business owners make that prevents them
from scaling and having that longevity?
Running out of cash is obviously number one.
And then it's people.
Talk to people in your organization
and it could ruin a culture.
So for me, it's all about culture and people.
We're always hiring way smarter people than me.
You're part of the top 1%.
What is it that you do
that the 99% of people don't do?
I want it.
I never doubted myself ever.
I've always wanted it.
But one last piece of advice, be giving.
Like, don't be just takers, right?
Like, business is relationships, right?
So when you look at a business, don't think about
it as a sale or a fee or a commitment
or anything like that.
That's horrible.
Think about how do you
maximize the value of your relationships?
That is really critical.
But be a giver, not a taker.
And I can promise you good things will happen.
My guy made $20 million in a single year.
He's a business owner.
He's been in finance for the last 25 years.
But I love what he said.
The biggest thing that took
him to eight figures was people.
People will take you places that money can't.
Take notes from that interview.
But let's go get this.
Next one.
All right, you guys.
My guy put up in
the Wraith out in Scottsdale, Arizona.
I'm going to go up to him, ask
him how he was able to afford this car.
This is a multi, multi $100,000 car.
We got to figure out what he did
to be able to afford this out here.
Let's go see what he has to say.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you, man.
Is this your Rolls Royce?
Yes, it is.
And what do you do for a living out
in Scottsdale to be able to own a Rolls, man?
What do you do for a living?
Oh, man.
I've been an entrepreneur for more than half my life.
But ultimately, I'm most known for building
one of the most successful oral care companies
online called Snow.
That's incredible, man.
How long have you been a business owner for?
Since I was 13 years old.
That's all I know.
And how much money is that
business going to generate you this year?
$200 million.
What is your secret to sales?
Our customers are our investors.
You treat your customer as best as you can.
You build products that work.
You choose a market that's got enough size.
And you do it over and over again.
And you recruit an incredible team.
Because without a team, you can't do anything, man.
I couldn't do it by myself.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
I grew up with very little.
Born and raised here in Arizona.
And I used to take the city bus.
And I had big dreams even back then.
So I know exactly what it's like being broke.
And that was one of my motivations
was, how do I change my situation?
And I would do whatever it
took to not be broke anymore.
And that's exactly what I did.
For somebody who's stuck in that cycle of poverty,
what's one thing actionable that someone can do right now
to really get their lives on track?
I would say surround yourself
with people doing better than you.
Never be the smartest person in the room.
Listen more than you talk.
And get really good at asking questions and following up.
And really just the art of people, man.
The art of communication and building relationships.
It is the number one skill
in business is communication by far.
How important has it been being
able to sell yourself and business
beyond just building a product or building
a good service for people to buy?
It's the biggest thing, man.
If you're not your biggest fan, it's very hard for
people to get on the bandwagon of what you're working on.
So you've got to have the conviction.
Think big.
Think it through.
Think what's in it for them before
you think what's in it for me.
And if you do that long enough, you won't
have to worry about what's in it for you.
It'll be handed to you, man.
I think that that's super, super important.
So we pulled up on that
guy backing in the Rolls Royce.
And his business is going
to do $200 million this year.
But the craziest part is that he started out broke.
He didn't come from the bottom.
He didn't come from a big
family and inherited all this money.
He just thought bigger than everybody else.
It goes to show you, no matter
where you are at in life right now,
as long as you think bigger
and take action, anything is possible.
Did you end up selling your company?
I took it public in 1993.
And I retired in 1995.
What was the name of that business?
Employee Solutions.
It was on NASDAQ.
We had over 300 employees.
How much money did that
business generate in a single year?
We were doing almost a
billion dollars a year in revenue.
You were doing almost a billion dollars?
A billion, yes.
What was the biggest thing that
took you to a billion-dollar company?
Very simple.
You get the right people
that's going to sell for you.
You've got to sell your company.
You've got to sell yourself.
And when we got bigger, we
had to go out to New York
and meet with the Merrill Lynch's
and convince them that our
company is going to keep growing.
And they'll push our stock, which they did.
And it multiplies.
And that's how you do it.
And among yourself and the most highly
successful people that you study and know,
what is that one trait that they have in common?
Street smart.
They know how to handle situations that
you don't necessarily find in a book.
How old are you now?
I'm 85.
And I'm taking care of myself.
I work.
I work out every day.
I play golf.
And I look up and
I believe that's where it's at.
And if you were to go back in
time and have a conversation with your 20-year-old self,
when you were starting from zero,
what's the best piece of advice
that you would tell your younger self?
Whatever you want to do, just keep going at it.
Because you could throw 10 things on
a wall, I don't care what it is,
and nine of them fall off and
you've still got that one up there.
You're ahead of the person that never tried.
Wow.
Sir, thank you so much for your time.
I really appreciate that.
Thanks, guys.
You've got incredible advice.
All right, you guys.
So we were just eating breakfast and I went
up to a table with three guys at it.
And that guy was like,
in the middle of the table.
And I asked him, were there any business owners here?
And he told me that he took
a company public back in the 1990s.
Little did I know that that guy's
business did over a billion dollars in revenue.
And the advice he gave, my favorite part
about that whole interview was when he said,
if you try 10 things, if nine
of them fall and one of them stick,
you're in a better position than
people that never tried at all.
One of my favorite interactions that
I've ever had running this channel,
Scottsdale has been absolutely insane.
Let's go get this next one.
How old are you now?
And how old were you when you became a millionaire?
And what was the best?
Financial decision that you've
made throughout your lifetime?
Buy real estate.
Yeah, that's it.
And then ultimately you buy real estate.
Don't sell it unless you need
the money or there's a better opportunity.
If there's a better opportunity, use the tax code
1031 exchange to be able to defer your tax.
And next thing you know, it's like playing Monopoly.
One turns into two, two turns
into four, and then you buy hotels.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
I had a real estate
brokerage, residential real estate brokerage.
What's the most amount of money that you
guys have sold in revenue in one year?
Total amount of home value sold 1.4 billion.
What was the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
If there's a lesson about money,
then I'm going to give it to you.
If there's a mentor or somebody taught
you throughout your career that has always stuck
with you, what's that advice that
you'd pass on to the younger generation?
You see me smiling because there's only one.
Money is like shit.
If you leave it in a pile, it stinks.
And if you spread it around, things grow.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Close to $2 million.
Give somebody the blueprint to becoming
a real estate millionaire in today's world.
Have more real estate conversations than anybody else.
At the end of the day,
in real estate, there's really three things.
You got to find a lead.
You got to find the money, right?
At the end of the day, because if you
don't have any money, you got to find people that
can bring you money.
And then the education to get the deal
closed or vendor partners like title companies and
lending to be able to get it done.
Something that I was taught in real
estate was find starters, estate planners, and enders.
Starters are guys that are getting started.
Estate planners are people who have a basic portfolio.
And enders are people who don't want to work anymore.
They don't have the energy, but they have the
asset base and the money to be able to
help you out.
And so with that information, if you go build
a small network, then you got to go hustle
and find the deal.
Once you find the deal, one of my favorite
sayings in real estate is the money will find
the deal.
I love it, man.
You got fucking phenomenal advice, man.
My guy's real estate brokerage sold over
$1.4 billion in value this past year.
And gave some incredible advice to all
those trying to start making money and creating
wealth in real estate.
Shout out to him.
Scott still has been absolutely insane.
Let's go get this next one.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
Sales.
Sales and leadership.
Yeah.
Well, sales when I was young.
And then leadership when I realized, well, maybe
I can sell and get paid what I'm worth.
But then if I could lead a bunch of people,
I could get a little cut on a bunch of people.
If you want to get
rich, sales and leadership's the way.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
I mean, this year right now, guys,
look, I'm going to give you a secret.
I'm 44 years old.
And, you know, I'm going to
make nine figures plus this year.
And I'm going to the 10.
I'm going to go to the billion dollar company.
I know I will.
But I want to tell you something.
I woke up at 39 years old.
Now, listen, when I was
younger, like you guys, I self-developed.
I went hard.
But I'm going to tell you this.
I had a lot of distractions along the way.
You know what I mean?
And here's the secret.
Most people are going to self-develop to a
certain point to make a certain amount of
money.
And then they're going to slow
down when they hit their dream.
So you guys need to
keep your dreams really fucking big.
Because if you don't, once you
hit your dream, you stop working.
So my shit's so big.
I watch people.
People go out and drink.
I'll care.
I'll carry club sodas around just watching people.
And I'm like, dude, these guys are fools.
And I'll watch them.
And I just, I dust them.
I smoke them.
I out self-develop them.
They've slowed down.
And that's why I keep growing.
And that's why they stay the same.
Have you ever been broke before?
I've been broke a million times.
I was broke my whole life.
And I'm not afraid to go broke again.
I'm afraid to let my family down.
I'm the one that sets the example
for what's possible in our fucking bloodline.
And I'm not letting them down.
And I don't mean my family family.
I mean my wife and my kids.
You'll understand this when you get older.
And you guys, a lot
of you guys have good families.
But there's your chosen family.
And there's your blood family.
And sometimes your blood family isn't the
one that supports you when you go bigger.
They actually hate on you.
Now, you're going to have a
few of them that'll stick with you.
But most of them won't.
Because they'll think that you're too big.
You're too great.
When really, you went on to do big shit.
And they should support you and fucking cheer you on.
Instead, they envy you.
Or they get jealous.
And then they hate on you.
And once you do that, I'm out.
You're not my family anymore.
But anyways, I've been broke.
And I'm not afraid of being broke.
Matter of fact, the most dangerous person
in any room is the broke motherfucker.
Because the broke motherfucker has nothing to do with you.
You'll lose and everything to gain.
What's been the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
Well, this will bring a lot of
heat from a lot of different places.
Because everyone's different.
I like cash.
I pay cash for everything.
I have nothing financed in my life.
From a Lamborghini, a Ferrari,
a G-Wagon, our building, our company.
It's all cash.
What does that mean?
I only buy what I can get
when I can pay cash for it.
So, I don't owe anybody any money.
And no matter what happened right
now, all my shit's paid for.
Also, it allows me to function differently.
I like to spend my money to be broke.
I don't want to go buy that G-Wagon.
If I can't pay cash for it.
Now, look.
If I have a $15,000 mortgage payment.
I'm giving an example.
And I watch you take $7,000 out in interest.
I'm going to punch someone in the face.
I'm wondering who just took my fucking $7,000.
Right?
And by the way, taxes are real.
You really have to pay them.
You can't write off everything.
And I know there's all these loopholes.
But I'm not trying to fuck with the IRS.
So, I'm just going to pay cash for everything.
You guys go do whatever works for you.
But I sleep like a baby at night.
Knowing my shit's all liquid.
So, my point is.
When you do that and play that game.
It doesn't.
Allow you to sit back and play comfort.
You have to attack.
And you have to hunt.
What has been Andy Elliott's secret to
sales over the last 20 plus years?
I believe a couple things.
Number one.
Self-belief.
I mean, I can tell you this.
If I'm talking to you.
Confidence is fucking everything.
You guys walk into rooms.
And you can tell people don't believe.
You can tell when people really ain't going
to do what they say they're going to do.
So, number one.
Confidence is a big deal.
And you'll never out earn your own self-worth.
So, if you don't think you're worth it.
You're not going to earn it.
Do you know how you can see
kind of like what you look like?
That's why I work here.
We talk about fitness.
Because you can see what you look like.
You can see in your mind what you
think you look like when you're going through something.
Dude, if you don't think you look
the best and you feel good about yourself.
You're not going to close that deal.
You're not going to make that thing happen.
So, one of my secrets is
I really believe in me, man.
I have a delusional belief in me.
Nobody can take that from me.
I can walk into any situation in any room.
I can close any deal.
I can shut down any client.
Don't tell me what ain't going to happen.
I'm going to tell you
what the fuck's going to happen.
When I show up, shit goes down.
You have to roll that way.
You can never let anyone convince you.
Think of that otherwise.
It can never happen.
But listen, sales is a skill.
Everything in life is a skill.
And I would tell you, if anybody wanted
to get rich, anyone, learn sales, learn leadership.
And this market will reward you in ways you've never
imagined if you've got good intentions and you like people.
Fucking phenomenal.
That was amazing.
All right, you guys.
We're on a mission to bring you guys value and advice
from some of the most successful entrepreneurs in the entire world.
And Scottsdale is one of the
wildest cities that we've ever filmed.
But we've got some incredible content on the way.
So like and subscribe for this amazing content to come.
And click here to watch our full video going
all over Dallas asking multi-millionaires how they became wealthy.